pixelfilmstudios.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy - Final Cut Pro X and Motion 5 Special Effects , Plugins, Transitions and Themes

#### PRIVACY POLICY

This site (the “Site”) is owned and operated by Pixel Film Studios (“Company”). This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you, the end user, about how we handle information we process on behalf of our clients who use our lead generation and online marketing services.   
This Privacy Policy applies to Company’s websites that link to this Policy. By using this Site you are accepting and consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any terms, please do not use this Site or submit any personal information. 

#### Children’s Privacy

This Site is not directed to children under the age of thirteen and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen on the Site. If we become aware that we have inadvertently received personal information from a visitor under the age of thirteen on the Site, we will delete the information from our records.

#### Information We Collect

Information collected by Company falls into two categories: (1) information that users voluntarily submit in connection with their use of the Site; and (2) tracking information recorded as a visitor or user navigates the Site.   
In connection with your use of the Site, you may choose to provide certain personal information. This information may include your name, address, phone number(s), email address, and credit card information (such as name, card number, expiration date and CVV code).  
We also collect tracking information that records visitors’ interactions with the Site. Like most Web site servers we use log files. Log files include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We match log file information with the personally identifiable information you voluntarily submit on the Site. 

Pages on our Site may contain "web beacons" (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). Web beacons allow third parties to obtain information such as the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, the type of browser used to view the page, and the information in cookies set by the third party. We use log files to store the data that is collected through web beacons and match it with the personally identifiable information you submit to the Site.

We may use cookies to collect information about your interaction with the Site. A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computer and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies record information about your online preferences. Cookies let us know about repeat visitors and if we are delivering quality products and services to our Clients. We may also use cookies to identify which sites our repeat visitors are coming from, so that we can place more of our online advertising on these sites, and can, where necessary, pay our affiliates and other business partners. 

#### How We Use Information We Collect

Company may use the information it collects (“User Information”) for any legally permissible purpose in its sole discretion. The following paragraphs describe how Company uses User 

#### Information

Company may generate aggregate reports for Site visitors to measure the performance of the Site. These reports may contain personally identifiable information.  
Targeted Advertising. Based on User Information, Company may attempt to customize and target advertising to an individual. Company may, at its discretion, target advertising to an individual on the Site, in email and/or through direct mail. Such advertising may be unrelated to the products or services offered or promoted on the Site.

Email. Company may use User Information to provide email marketing materials to users. Such email marketing may feature the goods and services of third parties, and may be unrelated to the products or services offered or promoted on the Site. Company may maintain separate email lists for different purposes.   
Direct Mail. Company may use User Information to advertise, directly or indirectly to individuals using postal mail. 

Use of Log Files and Cookies. Company may use Log Files or Cookie information (1) to match a user’s Log Files or Cookie information to personally identifiable information, (2) to track an individual’s web browsing habits, (3) to determine which areas of our sites are most frequently visited, (4) to track our affiliates’ performance in delivering visitors to the Site. This information helps Company to better understand the online habits of users so that it can attempt to customize and target advertising and promotions to users. 

Profiles of Users. Company may use User Information to make a profile of users of the Site. A profile is created by associating or matching the various sources of User Information. 

Storage of User Information. Company may store User Information in a database on secure computers. 

Sale, License or Transfer to Third Parties. Company may sell, license or transfer User Information to third parties for the purposes of sending you offers of goods or services via email, postal mail and/or telemarketing. This may include the transfer of your name, address, phone number, email address, IP Address, date/time you visited the Site, and evidence that you have accepted any terms on the Site (including the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy).

We may provide User Information to our third party affiliates, publishers, distributors and mailers for the purpose of compensating them for distributing advertising materials directing visitors to the Site, or that measures their performance or success in driving visitors to the Site.

Company may transfer User Information to third parties when necessary to provide a product or service that a user orders from such third party while using our Site. 

Legal Process. Company may disclose User Information to respond to subpoenas, court orders and other legal processes. 

Company may use User Information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or violations of our terms of use.

Sale or Assignment. We may share or assign User Information with or to a successor-in-interest or buyer in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. 

Summary Data. Company may sell or transfer non-individualized information, such as summary or aggregated anonymous information about users of our web sites as a whole or as sub-groups of users. 

#### Opt-Out Policy

You may exercise your option to not receive any future electronic communications from us by clicking here or writing to us at the following address:   
Privacy Officer Pixel Film Studios 120 Vantis, Suite 300 Aliso Viejo, CA 92656  
Please note that unsubscribing from this Site’s electronic mailings will not unsubscribe you from receiving communications from our affiliates, clients, partners or other third parties. You may still receive communications from third parties to whom we have disclosed your information prior to the time you opt-out. You should contact each third party in the event that you no longer want to receive information from such party. 

#### “Do Not Track” Requests

At this time Company does not collect personally identifiable about individual user’s online activities over time and across third party web sites or online services. However, it reserves the right to do so in the future without modifying this Privacy Policy. In the event Company does elect to collect such information, it will not honor Web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms that provide the ability to exercise choice with respect to such information collection.

#### Privacy Complaints

If you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by clicking here or writing to us at:

#### Privacy Officer 

Pixel Film Studios 120 Vantis, Suite 300 Aliso Viejo, CA 92656  
Please provide as much detail as possible as to how you believe that this Privacy Policy has not been complied with. We will investigate your complaint promptly. 

#### How to Access or Modify Your Information

We strive to keep all personal information accurate and complete. You can access or change your personal information at any time; provided, however, that we may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require disproportionate technical effort, risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical. We may also refuse a request to delete information if maintaining the information is required by law or is part of a fraud investigation, or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.   
You may access and modify your personal information by clicking here or writing to us at:

#### Privacy Officer 

Pixel Film Studios 120 Vantis, Suite 300 Aliso Viejo, CA 92656

#### Your Privacy Rights

Individuals who reside in California and have provided their personal information may request information regarding disclosures of this information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. Such requests must be submitted to us at the following mailing address:   
Privacy Officer Pixel Film Studios 120 Vantis, Suite 300 Aliso Viejo, CA 92656  
This request may be made no more than once per calendar year. We reserve our right not to respond to requests submitted other than to the address specified above. 

#### Links to Other Sites

We may provide links to other Web sites for your convenience and information. These sites may have their own privacy policies in place, which we recommend you review if you visit any linked Web sites. We are not responsible for the content of linked sites or any use of such sites. 

#### Security

We work hard to prevent unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. We have put in place commercially reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Although we take reasonable precautions to protect your data, we cannot guarantee the complete security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the internet. 

#### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we change this Privacy Policy, any changes will be updated on this page, with the date of last update located below. By continuing to use the Site after we post any changes, you accept and agree to the modified Privacy Policy.   
Last Updated: September 16, 2016. (view archived versions [here](https://store.pixelfilmstudios.com/previous-privacy-policies/))
